[Home](https://www.ivars.com/) Order Locations Menus Reservations [Group Dining](https://www.ivars.com/group-dining)

[Promos](https://www.ivars.com/promos) Store [Carte Clam](https://www.ivars.com/carte-clam) [Newsletter](https://www.ivars.com/newsletter) [Jobs](https://apply.jobappnetwork.com/ivars)

Back [Seafood Bars](https://order.online/business/26134/en-US) [Acres of Clams](https://order.online/store/ivar's-acres-of-clams-seattle-968977/?hideModal=true&pickup=true) [Salmon House](https://order.online/store/ivar's-salmon-house-seattle-41227/?hideModal=true&pickup=true) [Mukilteo Landing](https://order.online/store/ivar's-mukilteo-landing-mukilteo-969063/?hideModal=true&pickup=true)

Back [All Locations](https://www.ivars.com/locations) [Acres of Clams](https://www.ivars.com/acres) [Salmon House](https://www.ivars.com/salmon-house) [Mukilteo Landing](https://www.ivars.com/mukilteo-landing) [Seafood Bars](https://www.ivars.com/sfb-locations) [Stadiums](https://www.ivars.com/sports)

Back [Acres of Clams](https://www.ivars.com/acres-menus) [Salmon House](https://www.ivars.com/salmon-house-menus) [Mukilteo Landing](https://www.ivars.com/mukilteo-landing-menus) [Seafood Bars](https://www.ivars.com/seafood-bars/#seafood-bar-menus)

Back [Reservations](https://www.ivars.com/reservations-1) [Acres of Clams](https://www.exploretock.com/ivarsacresofclams?tock_medium=search_nav&tock_source=tock) [Salmon House](https://www.exploretock.com/ivarssalmonhouse?tock_medium=search_nav&tock_source=tock) [Mukilteo Landing](https://www.exploretock.com/ivarsmukilteolanding?tock_medium=search_nav&tock_source=tock) [Group Dining](https://www.ivars.com/group-dining)

Back [Gift Card Purchase & Balance](https://www.ivars.com/purchase-balance) [Shirts & More](https://ivars.mybigcommerce.com/)

Privacy Policy
==============

Terms and Conditions of Use of the IVAR’S (Ivars.com) Web Site
--------------------------------------------------------------

Please Carefully Read the Following Terms and Conditions

Use of the pages in the IVAR’S Web Site is dependent on your agreement to the following terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, you should not use this site.

Privacy Policy Downloadable Files
---------------------------------

Click below for a PDF (opens in new tab) or Word file format (option to save file):

* [**PDF File Format: Ivar’s Privacy Policy**](https://www.ivars.com/s/Ivars-Privacy-Policy-11-23.pdf) >
    
* [**Word File Format: Ivar’s Privacy Policy**](https://www.ivars.com/s/Ivars-Privacy-Policy-11-23.docx) >

Remedies & Compliance: How to contact Ivar’s about privacy concerns
-------------------------------------------------------------------

If you have questions or concerns regarding our collection and use of your Personal Information or any other privacy issues, please contact:

Ivar’s Inc.  
1109 1st Ave, Suite 350  
Seattle, WA 98101-2292  
Attention: Privacy Officer

Telephone: (206) 587-6500  
Email: [webmail@keepclam.com](mailto:webmail@keepclam.com?subject=Ivar's%20Privacy%20Policy)

Keep Clam & connect with us:
----------------------------
